A Finding Aid to the Colin de Land Collection, 1968-2008, bulk 1980-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.delacoli
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; Series 1; 12 Linear feet Box 1-12
  - Snapshots, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; 1.1
    - Venice Biennale, 2001 June (Box 11, Folder 12-18)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Frank Schroder, Kembra Pfahler, Julian LaVerdiere.
    - Wax Series of Fine Art, 2001 June (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and Kembra Pfahler at Kembra’s home; Patterson Beckwith and [Karen Hallock?].
    - Concave Serviette, Los Angeles, CA, 2001 July (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Kelbra Pfahler, the Girls of Karen Black at hotel performance art event in Los Angeles. Also includes photos of Colin de Land as a Girl of Karen Black.
    - Chloe Sevigny and Lizzi Bougatsos, 2001 October (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Includes photos of Chloe Sevigny and Lizzi Bougatsos in front of paintings by Steve Ellis; Colin de Land; unidentified collages/paintings. Contact sheet and negatives also include a series of photos of hardware.
    - American Fine Arts, 2001 November-December (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Includes photos of Stephen Shearer, John Waters, Spencer Sweeney, Colin de Land, Lizzi Bougatsos, Takahiro Imamura, Kembra Pfahler, New York street scenes including brick structure on a truck in Chelsea, artwork by Stephen Shearer, John Waters, and Spencer Sweeney.
    - Cher Concert, circa 2002 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Includes photos of Kembra Pfahler at a Cher concert.
    - Marlene McCarty Opening, 2002 January (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Includes photos of the opening reception for Marlene McCarty exhibition Poltergeist, Girls at Home (2002) at American Fine Arts, with Glyniss McDaris, Chivas Clem, Lizzi Bougatsos, Andrea Fraser, Harbour Fraser Hodder, Colin de Land, Frank Schroder, Takahiro Imamura, John Waters, artwork by Marlene McCarty and Gary Indiana. Also includes photocopy of photo of Kembra Pfahler.
    - Armory Show, 2002 February (Box 11, Folder 25-31)
      Includes photos by Peter Serling of Armory show visitors and booths.
    - Jack Pierson Exhibition, Miami, 2002 March-June (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Includes installation shots of Jack Pierson’s exhibition Regrets (2002) at the Museum of Contemporary Art, North Miami.
    - Availablism and Antinaturalism, 2002 March (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Includes photos of Kembra Pfahler in the exhibition Availablism and Anti-Naturalism: A Feminine Experiment & A Live Performance of A Star Is Born: The Horror Version Starring the Girls of Karen Black at American Fine Arts at Pat Hearn Art Gallery.
    - Serge Spitzer Exhibition, 2002 April (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Includes photos of Serge Spitzer exhibition Work from the 70s and 80s (2002) at American Fine Arts. Also includes photos of Takahiro Imamura, Jess Holzworth, Lizzi Bougatsos, Daniel McDonald, Serge Spitzer, Colin de Land, artwork by Garry Gross, and Marlene McCarty at American Fine Arts. Also includes photos of a beach vacation with Kembra Pfahler.
    - American Fine Arts, Pajama Portraits, 2002 May (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Includes photographs of Ned Ambler, Brian McPeck, Lizzi Bougatsos, Spencer Sweeney, Souhi Lee, and Kembra Pfahler at American Fine Arts, as well as a series of posed portraits of Colin de Land in pajamas.
    - Hal Foster and Colin de Land Portraits, 2002 May (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Includes a series of portraits of Hal Foster and of Colin de Land at American Fine Arts. Also includes photos of Lizzi Bougatsos, Christopher Sperandio, Brain McPeck, Spencer Sweenery, Jacqueline Humphries, Barbara Morse, and Howard Morse at American Fine Arts. Photo of Gareth James and Gardar Eide Einarsson artwork from Lars Von Trier exhibition at AFA appears on contact sheet but is not included.
    - American Fine Arts, Opening Reception, 2002 May (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Includes photos of an opening reception, likely not at American Fine Arts, with Hal Foster and possibly Robert Storr. Also includes photos at American Fine Arts of Takahiro Imamura, Daniel McDonald, Lizzi Bougatsos, and Margaret Deluccia.
    - Cape Cod, Summer 2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of Jack Pierson, Tom Borgese, Colin de Land, Spencer Sweeney, Daniel McDonald. Also includes series with Spencer Sweeney and others on the beach with fake blood.
    - Hat Photos and Alex Bag Exhibition, 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Includes a series of still life photos with Colin de Land’s Don’t Bother Me… hat, Colin de Land, Chivas Clem, Alex Bag, Daniel McDonald, Brain McPeck, and artwork by Alex Bag during exhibition Crackup (2002) at American Fine Arts at Pat Hearn Art Gallery.
    - New Orleans, 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 9-11)
      Includes photos of Jacqueline Humphries wedding in New Orleans, with Carol Greene, Spencer Sweeney, [Carlo McCormick?], and others. Also includes photos of John Waters exhibition Straight to Video, likely at Arthur Roger Gallery, with Mary Heilmann and John Waters at the opening reception.
    - New Orleans and Alex Bag Opening, 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of Jacqueline Humphries wedding in New Orleans, with Colin de Land, Spencer Sweeney, Mary Heilmann, and Carlo McCormick. Also includes photos of opening for Alex Bag’s exhibition Crack Up at American Fine Arts at Pat Hearn Art Gallery, with Glyniss McDaris, Matt McAuley, David Karlin, Takahiro Imamura.
    - Alex Bag, Crack Up Exhibition, 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Includes installation shots of the Alex Bag exhibition Crackup at American Fine Arts at Pat Hearn Art Gallery.
    - Art Basel, 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, John Armleder, Colin de Land, Frank Schroder and family, Roger Pailhas, skate ramp installation, artwork by Richard Prince, Henrik Olesen, Mary Heilmann, and Mark Dion, Art Basel booths.
    - Europe, 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Includes photos of art fair, possibly Art Basel or Art Cologne, with Colin de Land, Kembra Pfahler, Christian Philipp Muller, Esther Friedman, Georg Kargl, Christian Nagel, and [Beatrice von Bismarck?].
    - Vienna, 2002 June (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Georg Kargl, Carol Greene, and Esther Friedman. Also includes photos of Kembra Pfahler at home.
    - Colin de Land in the Hospital, 2003 March (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Includes photos taken by Dennis Balk of Colin de Land in the hospital.
    - Armory Show, 2003 March 7-10 (Box 12, Folder 19-24)
      Includes photos by David Willems of Armory show visitors and booths.
    - Pat Hearn Photographs, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 25)
      Envelope labeled Pat Hearn. Includes early photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, George Condo.
    - Pat Hearn Photographs, 1977-1980s (Box 12, Folder 26)
      Envelope labeled Pat Hearn. Includes photos of Pat Hearn and Colin de Land at home, New York street scenes, travels in South America, several photos of a stuffed panda with the catalogue Art and Language (Van Abbemuseum, Eindhoven, 1980), unidentified wedding, [Richard Prince?], one photograph of Colin de Land dated September 1977, and one photo of an unidentified concert.
    - Pat Hearn Photographs, circa 1980s-Early 1990s (Box 12, Folder 27)
      Envelope labeled Pat Hearn. Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Frank Schroder, Lisa Spellman, Chi Chi, unidentified couple at the Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art, available office space at 445 Avenue of the Americas, Epcot Center, Disney World. Also includes a holiday card from Constantin von Haeften and an altered photo of Craig Wadlin and others at American Fine Arts.
    - Pat Hearn Negatives, 1980s-1990s; This folder includes negatives from the collection of Pat Hearn. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified Negatives, 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
    - Unsorted Photographs (1 of 25), circa 1968-1980s (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Includes assortment of early photos of Colin de Land, some by Baird Jones, a dog with artwork, a 1968 photo of a woman, possibly Aleta Hamada, series of photos of a sign with religious symbols and the date 1968. Also includes a set of polaroids, some inscribed by Edward Braddocks.
    - Unsorted Photographs (2 of 25), circa 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Includes photos of Jeffery Deitch in Japan, Pat Hearn, Chivas Clem, Moyra Davey with her child, Colin de Land, an unidentified art fair.
    - Unsorted Photographs (3 of 25), circa 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Includes photos of opening reception for Walter Robinson spin paintings exhibition; Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Nan Goldin, Cris Moor, Mark Dion, Tom Burr, Howard Morse, Daniel McDonald, Jacqueline Humphries, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, Reverend Jen Miller, Barbara Morse, Nils Norman, Brain McPeck, Dan Graham, Lizzi Bougatsos, Esther Friedman; early photo of Colin de Land with Aleta Hamada, Dr. Hamada, and Colin de Land’s aunt; Mary Heilmann, Jack Pierson, David Carrino, Colin de Land in Cape Cod; Colin de Land and Pat Hearn in a still from karaoke video for Daniel by Elton John’ artwork by Jessica Stockholder; Jess Holzworth and Lizzi Bougatsos event.
    - Unsorted Photographs (4 of 25), circa 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Includes photo of Frank Schroder, Pat Hearn, and Colin de Land in front of 40 Wooster Street (labeled CDL Desk), a transparency of a Garry Gross Brooke Shields photograph, and a medium format negative strip of a portrait of Colin de Land in front a painting.
    - Unsorted Photographs (5 of 25), circa 1980s-2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Includes 1980s polaroids of Colin de Land and Pat Hearn, photos of Daniel McDonald, John Waters, Ania Corcilius, Colin de Land, Ingo Taubhorn, Mark Dion at American Fine Arts, and Pat Hearn with Chi Chi. Also includes large series of photos from the Concave Serviette event, California, with Kembra Pfahler and the Girls of Karen Black, including Colin de Land as a Girl of Karen Black.
    - Unsorted Photographs (6 of 25), circa 1980s-2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of Kembra Pfahler, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, the Marden family, Matthew Marks.
    - Unsorted Photographs (7 of 25), circa 1980s-2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Includes assortment of photos: Nils Norman and Daniel McDonald, Colin de Land; assorted portraits of Pat Hearn; Emergency Art Sale for Pat Hearn (1997); Bee In (2001); early photographs of Pat Hearn in a blond wig; Gramercy Art Fair, Miami (1997); John Armleder; Nan Goldin and Cathy Torsney; Frank Schroder; Paul Morris and Sam Grubman with Pat Hearn; Lizzi Bougatsos and Takahiro Imamura; Brice Marden, Jackie McAllister, Frank Schroder, Howard Morse at Colin de Land birthday; Lizzi Bougatsos and Jess Holzworth; Brain McPeck; Kembra Pfahler, Daniel McDonald, Mark Dion, Patterson Beckwith, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, Jackie McAllister, Nils Norman, Rene Green, Mariko Mori, Spencer Sweeney at American Fine Arts; early Colin de Land travels in Paris; 1997 Venice Biennale; Cady Noland exhibition; invitation mock up for Pat Hearn memorial show.
    - Unsorted Photographs (8 of 25), circa 1980s-2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Includes handwritten note from Magda with two enclosed photographs. Includes assorted photos of Colin de Land (one with note from Andrea), John Waters (one signed by Anastasie Croy, 1996), Jeffrey Deitch, artwork by Garry Gross and John Waters, Pat Hearn, Lizzi Bougatsos, Charlie Finch, Reverend Jen Miller, Spencer Sweeney, Shaun Caley Regen, Mark Dion, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, Mariko Mori, Patterson Beckwith, Claudia Schiffer, artwork by Dan Graham, Massimo Audiello, Daniel McDonald, Antek Walczak, Tom Borgese, Frank Schroder, Andrea Fraser, Takahiro Imamura, Bee-In.
    - Unsorted Photographs (9 of 25), circa 1980s-2003 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and Pat Hearn’s wedding; Colin de Land during chemotherapy; various photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Christian Nagel, Matthew Marks.
    - Unsorted Photographs (10 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Includes an image labeled New Years 1997 with Daniel McDonald and Colin de Land; rephotographed magazines, newspapers, and ads; Paris street scene; a performance with Craig Wadlin and Gillian Haratani; photo of McAllister jersey; rephotographed Mel Bochner piece; artwork. With photos of Patterson Beckwith, Rosalie Knox, Colin de Land, Daniel Karlin, Pat Hearn, Craig Wadlin. With signed Chris Moore [Cris Moor] photos of Shanna Shank, 1997.
    - Unsorted Photographs (11 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Jack Pierson, Chi Chi, [Magda?], and others.
    - Unsorted Photographs (12 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of Ania Corcilius, Mark Dion, Estelle Schwartz, Colin de Land, John Waters, George Gilpin, Claudia Schiffer, Daniel McDonald, Lisa Spellman, Pat Hearn, Spencer Sweeney, Jess Holzworth, performance by Gillian Haratani and Craig Wadlin, Wooster Street scene.
    - Unsorted Photographs (13 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Includes assorted photos of Peter Fend, Nils Norman, Daniel McDonald, Colin de Land, Patterson Beckwith, Margaret Deluccia, a rolodex, an event related to Fat magazine, Jess Holzworth, flooding on Wooster Street with the AFA truck. Includes a series of photos of Colin de Land filming a hamburger. Also includes three signed Chris Moore [Cris Moor] prints (1997) and an annotated Post-It note.
    - Unsorted Photographs (14 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of Julian LaVerdiere, Carol Greene, Craig Wadlin, Nils Norman, Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Jackie McAllister, John Waters, Fran Lebowitz, David Karlin; Sam Grubman, Christian Philipp Muller with Fantastic Sh*t press release, Christian Nagel, Georg Kargl, Peter Fend, Jess Holzworth, Almine Rech and Bernard Picasso; Nuart theater marquee with Cindy Sherman Office Killer; Mark Dion lemonade stand.
    - Unsorted Photographs (15 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Includes photograph of Colin de Land and Renee Green inscribed by Nils Norman; photos of Pat Hearn and Colin de Land; rephotographed Buddhist artwork.
    - Unsorted Photographs (16 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Includes an assortment of snapshots, most of which are included in the book Colin de Land: American Fine Arts. With photos of Colin de Land, Jean Stein, Spencer Sweeney, Rachel Harrison, Stuart Regen, Pat Hearn, Peter Fend, Marvin Kosmin, Christian Philipp Muller, Bee-In sign, James Welling, Moyra Davey, Reverend Jen Miller, Takahiro Imamura, Pat Hearn, Red Ed, Colin de Land as a Girl of Karen Black, Warren Neidich, Daniel McDonald, Rainer Ganahl.
    - Unsorted Photographs (17 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Includes portrait series, possibly by Patterson Beckwith, with David Karlin, Jackie McAllister; [Frank Schroder?]; Colin de Land and [Mark Kostabi?]; Polaroid of Colin de Land signed by Edward Braddock.
    - Unsorted Photographs (18 of 25), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Includes laminated Sagittarius horoscope; Postcards from John Waters, [Gottfried Tollmann?], and Patterson Beckwith; photo of Peter Fend and daughter with inscription; altered photo of Frank Schroder with inscription possibly from Colin de Land; snapshots of Pat Hearn, Kembra Pfahler, and Chi Chi; Polaroids of Colin de Land, Chi Chi.
    - Unsorted Photographs (19 of 25), circa 1990s-2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Includes two photographs: Sam Grubman, Paul Morris, and Pat Hearn; Kembra Pfahler, Colin de Land.
    - Unsorted Photographs (20 of 25), circa 1990s-2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Includes snapshots of Colin de Land, Rosalie Knox; a strip of photo booth pictures of Colin de Land and Peter Fend; a reproduction of a Colin de Land cartoon by Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio, Fantastic Shit Didactic, 1996; announcement for gallery talk Dealer As Educator: Colin de Land, February 22.
    - Unsorted Photographs (21 of 25), circa 1990s-2002 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Includes assorted photos of Colin de Land, Kembra Pfahler, a Bee-In, Richard Prince, Cady Noland exhibition, Craig Wadlin, Peter Fend, Chi Chi, Georg Kargl, Christian Nagel, Cris Moor, Christine Tsvetanov, Daniel McDonald, Takahiro Imamura, backstage at Bernadette Corporation fashion show, Massimo Audiello, Tom Burr, John Waters, Jeffrey Deitch, artwork by Peter Fend, Jacqueline Humphries, Carol Greene, Glyniss McDaris, Rachel Harrison, Daniel McDonald, Matthew Marks.
    - Unsorted Photographs (22 of 25), circa 1990s-2002 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      Includes assorted photos of John Waters, artwork by Cris Moor, Kembra Pfahler, Pat Hearn, Mary Heilmann, Jack Pierson, Daniel McDonald, Karen Hallock, artwork by John Waters, Carol Greene, Garry Gross, Frank Schroder, Julian LaVerdiere, Spencer Sweeney.
    - Unsorted Photographs (23 of 25), circa 1992-2002 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Kembra Pfahler.
    - Unsorted Photographs (24 of 25), circa 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of Hans Haacke letter protesting the Philip Morris sponsorship of the 1995 exhibition 1965-1975: Reconsidering the Object of Art, as well as letter signed by Michael Asher, Daniel Buren, John Knight, Douglas Heubler, Robert Barry, Sol LeWitt, Dan Graham, Lucy Lippard, Adrian Piper, and two others (illegible); Daniel McDonald and Craig Wadlin, Pat Hearn; party at American Fine Arts including James Welling and Moyra Davey; film canisters and Felix Gonzalez Torres catalogue; AFA and the Gramercy Art Fair of Cris Moor, Gillian Haratani, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Lisa Spellman, Rosalie Knox, Peter Fend, Jackie McAllister, Alex Bag, Patterson Beckwith and others; artwork by John Waters; Brigid Berlin performance at the Gramercy Art Fair.
    - Unsorted Photographs (25 of 25), circa 1998-2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      Includes assorted snapshots of group in Basel with Georg Kargl, Colin de Land, Christian Nagel, Christian Philipp Muller, [Beatrice von Bismarck?]; Mike Ballou, Ken Saylor, Judith Barry, Daniel McDonald, Gillian Haratani, Tara Delong, Blake Rayne, Pat Hearn, Haim Steinbach, Alice Kosmin, Marvin Kosmin.
  - Other Formats, circa 1977-2003; 1.2
    Found here are a range of photographic material including framed personal photographs, binders and portfolios of photographic prints, contact sheets, and negatives, and two CD-Rs containing digital photographs. The binders have been disassembled and their original order retained. These sometimes include more formal installation shots of gallery exhibitions, though the documentation is not exhaustive.
    - Dennis Balk, Shards-Splinters, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 29)
      Includes 11 photographic reproductions of Dennis Balk paintings. One is inscribed on the back.
    - Mounted Photographs, circa 1980s (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Includes a set of mounted black and white beach photographs, possibly of and/or by Mark Morrisroe or Richard Prince, and one color photograph labeled Repose, ’69, Newport, R.I., for Pat—yrs truly, Malcolm, 8/12/85.
    - Colin de Land Desk, circa 2000 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Includes two transparencies showing Colin de Land’s desk at American Fine Arts.
    - Framed Photograph, Chandler Hearn, circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Framed Photograph, Jack Pierson, circa 1980s (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Framed Photograph, Pat Hearn and Colin de Land, circa 1980s (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Framed Photograph, Pies, circa 1990s-2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Framed Photograph, Colin de Land at Walmart, circa 1990s (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Armory Show, 2002 February (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Includes a set of Xeroxed photographs of the 2002 Armory Show with the names of the pictured galleries inscribed below the images.
    - Installation Views Binder, 1980s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
      Includes contact sheets and negatives.
    - Negatives and Contact Sheets Binder, 1990s (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
    - Colin de Land Portfolio, 1990s (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Includes an assortment of photos and press clippings related to Colin de Land.
    - Colin de Land Portfolio, 1980s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Includes an assortment of snapshots and reproductions of images related to Colin de Land.
    - Miscellaneous Photographic Reproductions, circa 1977-2003 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      Includes an assortment of photocopies of snapshots, some snapshots, and a checklist for a Bernadette Corporation Fine Arts exhibition. Includes photocopied 1970s snapshots of Pat Hearn performing at Harry's Harborfront Club, Newport, RI, and photocopies of an event labeled AC5, October 22, 1996, perhaps a collectors’ seminar by Colin de Land.
    - Digital Photographs, circa 1990s-2003 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      Includes two CD-Rs marked “Colin de Land Photo Archives from G4 Laptop. Disk one holds 488 images. Disk two holds 331 images.
  - Slides, circa 1980s-2003; 1.3
    Slides document daily life within the American Fine Arts, Co. circle. Many are related to vacations in Cape Cod and art related travel in Germany, including trips to Documenta and the Koln Kunstmarkt. Subject matter may overlap with the photographs found in Series 1.1: Snapshots. Slides are arranged in rough chronological order.
    - New York, circa 1980s (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of New York street scenes, as well as portraits of [Mark Dion?].
    - Festival, 1980s (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and [Magda?] at a festival or party. Also includes photos of a bingo game.
    - Long Island, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Chi Chi, Frank Schroder, Green River Cemetery, car with inscription: Chi Chi, 39 Wooster Street, N.Y.C.. Also includes photo of one work of art labeled Benys.
    - American Fine Arts, 1989 September (Box 14, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Peter Fend, Angela Cumberbirch, Erik Oppenheim, [John Miller?], Pat Hearn, Massimo Audiello, and artwork by Peter Fend, John Miller, Gary Mirabelle, and Lawrence Weiner.
    - SoHo Galleries, circa 1990s (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Includes photos of Stricoff Fine Art, Magna Gallery, and Louis K. Meisel Gallery, with [Mark Dion?].
    - Koln, circa 1990s (Box 14, Folder 19)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Georg Kargl, Christian Nagel, Julia Scher, Jutta Koether, with others unidentified at an art fair in Cologne, with artwork by Cady Noland, Peter Fend, Jessica Diamond, Julia Scher, and artwork.
    - Scher at Rudolf Zwirner in Koln, circa 1990s (Box 14, Folder 20)
      Includes installation shots of Julia Scher exhibition at Rudolf Zwirner Gallery in Cologne, with photos of Julia Scher.
    - Las Vegas, circa 1990s (Box 14, Folder 21)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Las Vegas street scenes, Wayne Newton signage.
    - Holidays, circa 1990s (Box 14, Folder 22)
      Includes photos of holiday dinner with Peter Fend, Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, Pat Hearn. Also includes photos of Lincoln Center and Rockefeller Center.
    - American Fine Arts, 1990 May (Box 14, Folder 23)
      Includes photos of Jessica Diamond exhibition Money-Hole (1990) at American Fine Arts, Peter Fend, [Erik Oppenheim?], Margaret Deluccia, with artwork.
    - Stockh Empty Glass Slide, 1990 May (Box 14, Folder 24)
      Includes glass slides, some empty, one with Jessica Diamond Money-Hole (1990) installation shot. Labeled W. De With Stockh, copyright B. Goedewaagen.
    - Andrea Fraser, Nagel, 1990 November (Box 14, Folder 25)
      Includes installation shots of Andrea Fraser exhibition at Galerie Christian Nagel, Cologne, Germany.